Thank you for watching!
Thanks again for all your hard work
Hallo! Ste, this time with Rosy Chronicle's Honaka Hashida and
Rosy Chronicle's Hazumi Uemura!
This time, we'll be talking with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
This is the first time for both of us to MC for Halo! This is the first time for both of us to be MC of "Halo!
I'd like to introduce ourselves.
I'm 18 years old and from Tokyo, Hashida Honaka.
I love the character Cinnamon Roll from Sanrio, so I collect Cinnamon goods and I like to watch baseball games because I love the Chiba Date Marines.
My name is Hazumi Uemura, a 16 year old high school sophomore from Osaka, Japan, and a member of the Large Chronicle.
My hobby is drinking milk.
From my point of view, Hazumi is...
I have an image of her expressing her opinions without hesitation.
Rosy Chronicle: I've seen a lot of live videos.
We often exchange messages about what's wrong with it.
But they all say the same thing....
Also, Hana Shimakawa and Emi Soma have just joined the group.
Hana Shimakawa and Emi Soma have just joined the group, so they often don't express their opinions yet.
But Hasumi...
I think it's easy for them to notice things, and we often notice our mistakes and things we didn't notice before.
From my point of view, Honoka-chan, the leader, is like this, she expresses her opinions like we just did, and when we argue, everyone expresses their opinions, but there are times when we split up.
At that time, the leader summarizes the opinions and says, "Let's put them this way or that way.
I'll do my best.
I'm still working hard as a leader.
As for my recent activities, I have performed at many events.
In 2024 alone, we have performed at more than 10 festivals and events.
Do you have any memorable moments among them?
I, Uemura, recently performed at an event called Mar Portum 2024.
It was held in Shinnishibashi, Osaka.
It was a long performance, lasting 40 minutes.
It was quite a long performance, 40 minutes.
During the MC at the event, the fans said "Welcome back.
I still have a great memory of the fans saying "Welcome back.
I have a great memory of that time.
Yes, I thought I had to say "welcome back" at that MC.
I thought I had to say "Welcome back" for sure.
I had to say it.
Thank you very much.
And as for me...
When we performed at CRO FES
It was our first experience to perform in the rain.
The audience, we were on the stage with a roof over our heads.
but the audience had no roof over their heads
We were soaked to the skin.
We were soaked to the skin, and we saw so many people cheering us on.
We had to make sure that the audience was excited.
I remember how we gave it our all and performed in the rain.
And this weekend
Galafest in Gotanda
Galafest Autumn Appetite Exciting Present
and NANA FES in Osaka
NANA FES in Osaka.
And on November 19th
I will be a back dancer for JuiceJuice
for the first time as a group
at the Nippon Budokan
the Nippon Budokan for the first time as a group.
I've been an opening act before
I've done it before, but
But as a member of Logi Chronicle
but this is the first time for me to perform in the main
I'm going to do my best to make the audience excited.
I will do my best to make the audience excited.
Now, please watch this video.
Happy birthday, Mizuho!
Happy birthday to you, Mizuho!
Happy birthday!
I'm home.
Let's keep smiling and doing our best, just like everyone else's house!
Camerian, fur!
Still more!
Free loveable if you only fantasize about it
It's a strange history, love love love
Free loveable if only in your fantasies
Strong and princess
Maine dancing in the night Beauty hall
Reborn Miracle of Dreams
You For
Embrace me, seriously rosé
Lonely and tearful and shoo
But the times are wise
They're gonna make you strong
You, you, you, you, you
You, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
I want to see it
Move me the most
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love
I want to be loved, loved, loved, loved, loved
Let my desires fly beyond
Without all that
Scarier than ever
Sweet love
I'll get a cavity
The heart that eats
Violent
Even when I say no
Even when I'm mad
I want to be loved
Just push my hand
Go for it, Shah!
Li'l
O belum
só
someday
las
um
sz
More
or
s
lo
More
opposite
Regeneration
It's.
Knox
AI
COC
l
Shake me once more.
Uncle runner who will drown
Always looking back at your work
Wet the road
Even if my hand comes out
I'll ride it out for an hour
Make your dreams come true
Good night
Tsubaki Factory
Seino! This is Tsubaki Factory!
We just finished our live tour 2024 Autumn Kodo Shinjuku Lenny!
How did you like it?
It's been a while since we've done the tour itself, but so many of you called out our names, and I could feel the excitement directly from the audience, which I thought was really fun.
So, how about you, Fumika-chan?
Yes, this tour is very close to the audience, so I wanted the audience to pay more attention to the expressions on their faces.
Now, Yun-chan.
Yes, I did.
I want people to see our facial expressions because we are really close to each other on a live house tour,
The audience's expressions are also directly conveyed to us, so it makes us very happy to hear their reactions directly,
I would like to do my best to make the tour even more exciting.
So, the fall tour will continue, so please come and join us.
This is Tsubayu Factory.
This is Rosy Chronicle's Honaka Hashida and
Rosy Chronicle's Honaka Hashida and Hasumi Uemura present Haloste.
I would like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I will ask you a few questions.
I will ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly and at a good tempo.
I'll do my best.
What's the biggest change since you became a member of Rosy Chronicle?
I've become more of a comedian.
What is the ideal idol you are aiming for?
Ami Ishida of Morning Musume。 24
Tell us about a funny incident that happened in Rosy Chronicle recently.
There is something wrong with Yoshikazu Onoda.
The key to today's eye makeup is
Eyelashes
Tell us about your current goals as Rosy Chronicle.
I want to do a solo tour!
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you've all been wondering... about the incidents that have been going on in Rosie Chronicle lately.
I'd like to hear about it... but I don't know about this...
I'm just asking because I'm a woman... but I'm a professional trainee in Hana.
When she was a trainee I had an impression of her as a quiet girl, but recently I've been thinking that she's been a little too shy.
But lately, I have the impression that she's been going out of her way.
She tells me she likes me or loves me or thinks I'm cute every five seconds or so, and in that way she's very open.
When I was at the school, everyone was getting ready for the show, but there were times when I wandered around by myself and told each member how much I loved them for about 30 minutes.
But as a member, I'm very happy to see him.
And that eye makeup... since I joined Rosy Chronicle, I feel like Hasumi's eye makeup has been evolving more and more.
I don't know...
It's fun to look at the makeup tools and stuff, and I'm thinking that if I apply it this way, the color will come out better at school.
I've been looking at makeup tools and I'm having a lot of fun looking at them and thinking about how to apply it in a certain way to get the right color for school, and also eyelashes and stuff.
When I was a trainee, I was afraid to use my eyelash curler, but recently I've been using it a lot.
It's evolved a little bit.
Hasumi always makes sure that her eye makeup is perfect.
Not just the eye makeup, but the makeup itself.
And the makeup doesn't come off at all.
I think that's amazing.
I have almost all the same makeup tools as Hasumi.
It's like I have this for every eye that I don't even have the same one for.
If I use it well, it might be makeup that doesn't fall off.
My question to Honoka came after the VTR.
Anyway, today I'm going to try to go one or two steps ahead in staging.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
This time we are going to perform discotically.
I'd like to say it's very discotic.
As you explained to me earlier...
I want to forget about everything and have fun together.
The setlist and so on.
The set list and so on.
And the stage...
Yes.
I don't know, it's kind of unusual to have a stand.
I think it's quite unusual to have a stand on top of the stage.
I think it's going to be a very fun concert where everyone can make a lot of noise.
I think it's going to be a live performance that everyone can get excited about.
Music
We haven't decided on the content yet, but it's the dance part of the bungee jump for 6 years.
I've never done this before.
Up until now, we have never featured Shino Satoyoshi and myself, Mio Hirai, in the dance part of a BEYONES concert.
So I asked the staff to feature us in the dance part.
So I asked the staff directly.
So I asked the staff directly and asked them if they could create such an opportunity for us.
So I asked the staff directly and asked them if they could create such a venue for me.
So I asked the staff directly and it came true right away.
I'm very happy!
The book of goods introduction
It's so nice to the touch.
It's lightweight and easy to spin.
It's so cute!
It's like that one in town. I'll work hard, I'll work hard, I'll work hard, I'll work hard, I'll work hard.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Next, I'd like to ask Honoka a question.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Okay, here we go.
You've been the leader of Rosy Chronicle for about 3 months. What do you value as a leader?
To organize everyone's opinions.
What skill do you want to improve?
Selfie-taking skills.
Honoka is a big fan of the Chiba Lotte Marines professional baseball team. Throwing out the first pitch.
What do the members of Rosy Chronicle mean to you? They are like younger sisters.
From the leader's point of view, what are the strengths of the Rosy Chronicles? The purity of our members.
Thank you very much. I was wondering if you are a big fan of the Chiba Lotte Marines professional baseball team?
What would you like to do? I sometimes introduce myself by throwing out the first pitch, but if someone asks me that question, I'm sure I'll say "the first pitch.
I've always loved baseball since I was a little girl.
I've loved it since I was a little kid. It's always been my dream since I was watching baseball.
Standing on the mound and throwing out a pitch is an experience that is not easy to come by.
I've been practicing so that I'm ready for any job that comes my way.
That's great.
My brother used to play baseball, and he taught me.
I'm practicing so that I can throw with a glove.
Anytime.
That's great.
I'll be there.
For you, Hanaka, Rosie Chronicle is like a sister.
is like a little sister to Hanaka-chan, isn't it?
I graduated from high school.
I graduated from high school, but we're all still in school.
I saw them playing tag during recess.
Like I said before, there was a very school-like atmosphere.
There was a very school-like atmosphere.
It's like everyone is like a little sister.
In fact, Rena Kamimura, a member of the group, is the same age as my sister.
She's the same age as my sister.
I wanted to be like a big sister in Tokyo.
I've been thinking about it ever since Rena joined the group, and now that I'm in the position of leader, I feel even more strongly that she's like a little sister to me.
From my point of view, Honoka-chan is just like an older sister.
Really? I'm glad to hear it.
I'm glad. We'll continue after this.
I'll be right back.
I'm Mei Sugihara, a 12-year-old junior high school freshman from Hyogo Prefecture.
Music
I have loved dancing since I was a little girl. One day, my friend's mother recommended me to audition for Hello Project,
After watching Hello Project's music videos and live performances, I decided that I wanted to be a part of Hello Project.
I watched videos on the Hello Project trainees' channel, and I found that my senior, Rikako Sasaki, whom I admired so much, was always telling me that I had to be serious about what I was doing.
She said that if you don't do it seriously at any time, you will be overtaken soon.
I thought, "I want to be like that, too.
There are so many that I can't narrow it down.
I can't narrow it down, but recently I've been listening to
I'm thinking of becoming a heroine by Berry's Workshop.
Ai ha Kimi ni Nakaide ni" (Love is always inside of you)
Watching "Halopro Dance Academy" and
and collecting chick merchandise.
I love chickens so much that I have a key chain, a pencil case and stickers of them on my bag at school.
My favorite colors are milk blue and lemon yellow.
When I was little, I always liked different colors.
I thought milk blue was really beautiful at first glance.
Lemon yellow is the color of one of my seniors, Rikako Sasaki, whom I admire.
Rikako Sasaki, who is one of my favorite members.
Yellow seems to shine more brightly than anything else
Chick is yellow, too.
My favorite sports are dancing, which I have been doing since I was little
jumping jacks and basketball.
My favorite food is udon noodles made by my mother
fruit candy and zucchini.
I really like regular udon too.
My mom serves them.
and chopping the vegetables and seasoning them for me.
It's delicious on a global level!
I have never failed to make a fruit candy once!
The only ingredients to make candy are sugar and water.
I feel like I can almost do it if I only have amazing fruit.
I use a frying pan when I can.
I use a frying pan when I can, or when my mom is cooking.
It is also easy to use the microwave oven.
If you run out of fruit and have only candy left over, you can make another light candy.
You can also make another light candy.
I am often called MESA, with the "E" in MESA changed to a stretchy stick.
A lot of people always tell me I look like I'm having fun!
It's a little bit presumptuous of me to say.
I have a lot of friends and I can dance.
I'm sure I have 100 friends from nursery school and beyond!
I'll tell you about my morning routine. I wake up, brush my teeth and wash my face, but sometimes I fall asleep twice.
Then I make and eat breakfast, put on sunscreen, do my hair, pack my water bottle and lunch box.
But she only has about 30 minutes from the time she wakes up to the time she leaves the house, so in a word, Meisa has that blazing fast morning routine.
But I think this is a bad idea, so I'm going to fix it. Junior high school is a lot of fun, and it's great.
Thank you so much!
I don't know if it's okay.
It was really hard to balance dancing and singing at the same time.
It was physically demanding.
I did a lot of research and worked really hard on my lung capacity and so on.
I had no experience in singing, so I practiced a lot.
I had to practice a lot.
Who is who?
From the very first lesson
I knew I was going to win the dance competition.
I was so happy to receive an amazing dance award
I was so happy that I cried.
Of course, my goal now is to make my debut
But the challenge for me is
is to make my high notes more beautiful.
In order to correct my current issues
I will work hard to improve my physical strength
I will give a performance that shines brighter than anyone else's.
Thank you for watching.
I want to hurt you
I do I do Love tamer
Let's go beyond this
Let's fly This Kiss my
Proof of my resolve
I do I do
Let's fly
This time's Halo Pro trainee corner was Meimi Sugihara!
I had the chance to talk with Meimi Sugihara when I was a trainee of Halo Pro.
When I graduated from high school, she wrote my congratulations on a piece of candy in her handwriting on the spot.
The sweets had a cherry blossom pattern because it was spring.
So my family congratulated me a lot, but I also got a lot of congratulations from the trainee members.
I was very happy to receive congratulations from the trainee members as well.
Also, Meimi Sugihara has a great Kansai dialect.
She speaks in Kansai dialect, which makes me feel really close to her.
She's like a little sister to me.
And we, Rosy Chronicles...
We performed at the trainee presentation "Hottogisu" in September.
It was our first performance since we became Rosy Chronicle.
How did you feel about it?
We had to rehearse for Hello Project's concert and
and the Hello Project concert.
That's right.
At the Hello Project concert, I had the chance to travel around the country with the other members of the project.
I was able to grow in some areas by performing with them.
So when I perform with the Hello Project trainees and guests at the trainee presentation, I think it's a great opportunity for me to grow as a performer.
We Rosy Chronicles were determined not to be defeated in the space.
Yes, I, Hashida, had the opportunity to perform "Mirai Hajimari" at the Hello Project concert.
I think most of the audience didn't know us at the first performance.
But as we performed more and more times, we received more and more cheers from the audience.
I felt that our songs have been spreading to more and more people at the trainee presentation as well.
Please look forward to the next issue of Halo Pro Trainees Corner!
This is Miyabu Natsuyaki. Hello Kitchen has begun. This time, we asked this member to join us.
I'm Natsume Natsume, the tea lady. Please give my best regards to her.
I'm Natsume Nakayama, the tea lady.
Yes, please take good care of her.
Now, what would you like to make this time?
Yes, today we are going to make Soumen noodles.
I'm looking forward to it.
Here are the ingredients.
Okay, so, let's see.
You have appeared on Hello Kitchen before.
How is your cooking?
Well, since my last appearance
I started to cook a lot.
I used to not cook by myself at all.
But nowadays I cook for myself every day.
I've been working in the kitchen.
So I guess we can expect a lot from you today.
I'm not sure what I'm going to cook.
Yes.
It's pretty simple.
Tea is stronger.
Yes, it's strong.
I have high expectations for today and this time.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's cut the ingredients.
First of all, let's start with Spam.
Do you know what Spam is?
Of course I know what it is.
But I don't use it at home.
But you don't use it at home, do you?
That's right.
I had Spam onigiri when I went to Okinawa.
Cut it about 1cm thick.
About 3 pieces in the middle.
Yes, I understand.
You're getting good at this.
I'm glad.
You said you were going to cook the roots.
The way you handle the knife is totally different.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Shred it.
We're going to cut the whole thing into small pieces.
Today's recipe, or rather, dish is
I'm going to use what I have at home.
You can do it with leftovers.
That's for sure.
What kind of dishes have you made recently?
Lately I've been making things like salmon baked in foil.
It's pretty easy to make.
But I'm really into pork wrapped cabbage.
I shred cabbage and wrap it around pork.
It's pretty easy to make in the microwave.
It's also a great way to get vegetables.
I've been using it lately.
Oh, that's nice.
I got it in one go, really. You're getting good at it. You've improved a lot.
That's wonderful. The teacher is happy. I'm so happy.
I was so miserable last time that I didn't even know how to cook rice properly.
So you're going to make a revenge version? That's nice.
I'm going to cook 50 grams of onion now.
Yes.
Corn.
I just break them into pieces.
Are you into something? I like to do things.
Well, I'm looking for a place to live.
I feel like I've heard that one before.
You think you've heard that before?
Yes, that's right.
So, what kind of things? We talked about it.
We did talk about it.
I don't really want to move,
I've been looking for a place for a long time.
I can understand that. Yes, I understand how you feel.
The feeling of looking. It's not that I'm looking for a place to move,
I'm not really looking to move, but I get curious and look at them. I'm pretty picky about properties,
So I don't use one app, but two or three.
I use two or three apps to find properties that I like.
What are you particular about?
I like to cook these days, so I'm very particular about open kitchens.
I like open kitchens, so to speak.
Yes, that's right.
I search for apartments with this kind of open kitchen in my criteria.
What do you care about?
Do you care about the entrance?
The living room?
Yes, of course.
I didn't think we could get so excited talking about properties.
I didn't expect to be able to talk so much.
Like maisonette apartments?
Wow, that's nice.
I admired it.
And food, too.
I've accumulated a lot of food.
Besides looking for a place to live, I'm into wet rice crackers.
I'm addicted to wet rice crackers.
Yes.
Why did you get into this?
I got hooked on them because...
Well...
For a while, I don't know how to say it.
I wanted to try rice crackers and Japanese sweets.
I wanted to try wet rice crackers.
but I didn't have a chance to try it.
Then I happened to buy some wet rice crackers I found at a pharmacy.
I realized how delicious they were and
I started dancing.
I see...
I thought it was because he was still young, so he went to his grandma's house and she gave it to him, but if it was from himself...
But there's a rumor that she got wet rice crackers as a birthday present.
Kitahara Momochan, a member, asked me what I wanted for a present.
So I told her I wanted wet okaki, and of course I got wet okaki, but I also got wet okaki.
I'm going to use two eggs this time, but I'm going to go to Hello Kitchen and cook from there.
I'm going to use two eggs this time.
I can see that I'm doing a good job.
I'm so happy!
It all started with the butter chicken curry from last time!
Really?
Did you make the butter chicken?
No, I didn't.
I made curry.
Butter chicken is a bit...
It's a long process.
But I made curry for my family.
And they ate it.
That's great!
Now, let's put the eggs in.
With a pinch of salt.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Here you go.
Chopsticks, then.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Here they go.
Here you go!
A little more.
Yes, you can cut the white meat a little more.
But it would be great if we had a kitchen as big as this.
It would be great.
Then you can wash dishes here.
You can do whatever you want.
You can put it in the back.
Wow, it'll be great.
I know, right?
You were looking forward to it, weren't you?
I was really looking forward to it.
I'm glad.
Such a spacious kitchen.
I can do it.
It's done.
Yes, it's done.
Now, let's move on to frying the eggs.
Here's Miyamizu's point.
Make the eggs fluffy.
You can do this without teaching, right?
No, but fluffy?
You can do it.
What do you mean?
You're right.
What kind of technique?
I see.
It's a little bit like scrambled eggs.
It's a little more cooked, though.
I imagine it's cooked over high heat, with a little more oil.
When you put them in, they start to rise.
Then, turn it slowly.
I'm going to let it get airy.
Okay, here we go.
Put in half of the oil.
Slowly.
Now take the other half of the roll and turn it the other way.
Give it a quick stir to get the air in.
That's good, right?
This one! And this one!
Nice! It's so fluffy!
That's good! I've never seen eggs like this!
Maybe it's okay.
I'll put this one out.
Oh, my gosh! So fluffy!
I've mastered the Miyagi point!
That's what I'm talking about!
Well, that's all for this time!
That was fast!
It's too good!
Isn't this the best one so far?
Yes! It really looks like something you'd do at home.
I'm so happy!
You look so much lighter than usual.
You look a little teary.
Yes! I'm so happy.
Just like a father.
I was happy to see that too.
Like a father or a mother.
So, I'm sure that next time, things will go smoothly.
Let's do our best, and that's all for now.
Bye bye!
I like the sesame oil.
Looks delicious!
I think I can eat it now.
Delicious!
Rosy Chronicle's Honaka Hashida and
and Kasumi Uemura of Rosy Chronicle.
From here, we'd like to let you know a little bit more about us.
We have heard that people who know us well have answered our questionnaire.
I would like to introduce them to you.
First of all, the person who answered our questionnaire about Honaka Hashida is
Momo Kitahara from Ocha-no-Ma!
This is Momo-chan!
Let me introduce her answers.
Yes, ma'am.
Impression of Honoka Hashida
The answer is that Honoka Hashida told me she was a second grader at her first lesson after joining the Halo Pro trainees.
I thought it was great that she was a second grader.
In fact, she was in the second year of junior high school at the time.
She was that small and cute.
I mean, that impression still holds true today.
She still is.
I'm a little concerned about the "small" part, though.
Always.
This is really true.
I'm also a sophomore.
Maybe I'm wrong, too, but...
I'm in the second grade.
But when I went to my first lesson, I was imitating the other trainees who had joined with me.
But when I went to my first lesson, I imitated the other trainees who had joined with me.
I was also small, so I thought everyone was older than me.
I was really surprised that I was the oldest.
The next thing that impressed me about Motoko Hashida was how well she talked.
She has been in charge of MCing the corner of the trainees' presentation for a long time, and I think she's good at improvising.
Thank you very much.
I've always wanted to be an MC for the talk corner... and I saw Mr. Yanagimura and Ms. Ishiguri do it when I was a trainee.
I thought it was really cool that they talked with a script in their hands.
I thought it was really cool to hold a script and talk.
I like comedians a lot.
I often watch variety shows.
It's not so much that I try to learn on my own.
I'm not trying to learn by myself, but rather naturally absorb from them.
I often want to respond in this way.
It's not that I'm good at improvising.
It's more like you like to improvise.
Yes, I do.
Is that so? I like to improvise.
I'm glad you think so.
Next.
A side of Honoka Hashida that only I know
Honoka Hashida is a tsundere.
Honoka says she has a crush on Momochan.
But when it's just the two of us, Honoka is more of a spoiled brat.
That's not true.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't think so.
A spoiled brat.
I don't think it'll go that far. I think you have a crush on her.
I like you, Momo, but it's a one-sided love that's too heavy.
It's like this, but... they're not exactly two halves of the same person... but the weight of their love is different.
I don't want you to misunderstand that I like her but the weight of our love is different
I'm not aware that I'm carrying it, but I'm aware that I'm playing, otherwise the love will get heavier and heavier, so I'm trying to prevent that.
Thank you very much.
Next, we have Miku Nishizaki from Ocha-no-Ma, who answered our questionnaire about Hazumi Uemura.
Miku.
Let's get right to it... my impression of Hasumi Uemura.
I'm sure you'll be able to find out more about her personality as well as her looks.
I love Mikuku because she's been my heartbeat machine since I was a trainee at Spring Pro and we've been together for a long time.
But he calls me his granddaughter.
She's already called you that?
She calls me "big sister," not "little sister.
She calls me her grandson.
She's not my daughter anymore.
She's my grandson.
Okay, let's move on.
What do you think is strange about Hasumi Kamimura?
She drinks milk forever.
She says...
I think so too.
What's so strange about that?
Milk is my life partner.
That's true.
I've lived with milk my whole life, so it's normal for me.
I've been drinking milk forever. It's normal. It's not strange.
But you really do drink it. How much do you drink a day?
A day? I mean, I've never counted, you know, liters or anything like that, but I don't think anyone has.
I don't think anyone does. I don't think that's very common.
Morning, noon and night.
I drink it morning, noon, night, and after taking a bath.
I see... but even before and after rehearsals...
I drink half a bottle before and half a bottle after.
So I'm probably drinking at times other than the ones I just mentioned.
I really do drink forever.
Then I'd like to move on to the next question.
I'm the only one who knows this side of Uemura Hazumi.
I think she's a very cool woman who looks frail but has a strong Kansai spirit.
Yes, that's right.
She's a cool girl.
But as a Kansai person, I know she has Kansai spirit.
I think it's great, don't you?
I think it's really great. When we have lessons, Hazumi always carries a tote bag, but her mother told her to wash it,
She washed it once, and the bag that came out instead was a large gourd-shaped bag.
I even asked her where she could find such a bag.
Oh, no? What did you do with it? He said his mother gave it to him.
I thought it was very Kansai to have such a bag as a matter of course.
But you're a really hot girl, that's what I wanted to say.
Really?
She's a hot girl at first. She's really hot.
That's because I have it.
Anyone can be cool if they have leopard print.
I see. Then you should have one too.
Japanese people should bring their own leopard print to live shows, too.
I'd love to come!
I hear that's a good idea....
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
I love your hard work the best.
Kato Hashida Hono of Rosy Chronicle
Haloste, brought to you by Hasumi Uemura.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
This is our first time to MC at Haloste.
How was it?
I felt like a dash before I came here.
I was so excited to be here.
But when I saw this background
I thought, "Wow, this is the screen
I was so excited and relaxed to talk with you.
This was the first time for me and Hashida to work together as a Logy Chronicle, and the first time for both of us to work together like this.
I was really worried about whether I could speak properly or not.
But you know...
There were questionnaires from Momochan and Miku Nishizaki.
With that kind of support from the people around me
I think we had a lot of fun during the recording.
Here's an announcement.
On November 11th, Harodori Presents
Chronicles of Rosy Chronicles
Future Beginnings" will be held on November 11th!
This will be my first Rosie Chronicles event.
We will do our best to make it fun!
And on November 19th at the Nippon Budokan
We have organized the Halodori Presents!
JuiceJuice Concert Tour 2024
Triangle 2 Special.
Rosie Chronicle will perform as a back dancer!
This will be my first experience as a back-up dancer.
I will do my best to warm up the venue!
And on October 12th
Gala Festival Autumn Appetite Exciting Present!
NanaFest on the 13th
Giga Giga Sonic on the 19th
And on November 9, we will perform at Siga Idol Collection.
We will perform at many events this fall, so let's have fun together!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so be sure to give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Our partners were Rosie Chronicle's Honaka Hashida and Hasumi Uemura!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!